{
    "id": "1826e481854a4cf087d39a2fbeb5ca8d",
    "title": "Ever and never | Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3f832936ed7646c0b556b029f7dff7fb",
            "title": "Ever And Never | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have …………………. been to a foreign country.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you …………………. seen her perform?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you ……………….. go to Ireland on holiday?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I shall ……………….. remember you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "always",
                        "ever"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you ………………… go to live concerts?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Nobody …………………. visits them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ………………… seen a ghost.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….want to see you again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t ………………. want to see you again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hardly …………………. see my brother or sister.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}